If you want my help through the entire process of getting your college essays ready from writing
your Common App essay to completing your supplementals, then this is the right package
for you. I got into every single college I applied to with over $600,000 in scholarships
and a full tuition scholarship to Vanderbilt, and I've taught that same strategy to help
over a thousand students now write amazing college essays that have gotten them into great
schools like Penn, UC Berkeley with scholarship, Dartmouth, Cornell, Rice, NYU with full tuition
scholarship twice, and I would love to help you too. Here's how this package works. We'll start
with your Common App essay. If you're just starting from scratch, I will help you from
the very beginning to brainstorm ideas, figure out which of them is your best, create a detailed
outline for the best idea, help you add in the right kinds of details to your essay, and help
you refine it and polish it until it is ready to go and will 100% move the needle in a positive
direction for you. Then after that, we'll use the remaining calls that we have to work through your
supplementals for your colleges. I have worked with so many students on supplementals and so I
can help you with all of the big supplemental essays like your Y major essay, your YS essay,
the community essays, and more. I have worked with so many students on the school-specific
prompts, so I know exactly how to make those school-specific supplementals stand out, and that's
what I'm going to help you do. We are going to make sure that your supplementals are polished,
unique, have good hooks, etc., and by the time you finish this package, your Common App should be
ready to go, as well as most of your supplementals, which will be an amazing feeling. You will have
everything that you need to have both of them done. Finally, we can also work on your activity
list if we still have time remaining. So how do the calls work? Each call is a live 30-minute
one-on-one session with me. I don't have a team. I do all of the calls myself, and I'll be helping
you through every single step of the process. And you will also get unlimited email support
in between every single call to make sure that you're never stuck or second-guessing what
you're supposed to be working on or what you're supposed to do. We can space out the sessions
however you need. Most students do one call a week, but if you have tight deadlines, we can
definitely do multiple calls a week or schedule them however you need it. This package is meant to
make everything easier on you. The whole process should be so much less painful when you have the
package, because you will know what to do every single step of the way. That is the goal. If you'd
rather not schedule calls, I also have a written, edits-only version of the same package. But if
you're ready to get started working one-on-one with me, I am so excited to work with you. Email
me at avigallangatgmail.com if you have any questions before booking, and otherwise you
can book right here on this page.